<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog</title>
    <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Americas_06/Blog</link>
    <description>Well it sure was a comprehensive tour of Canada and the USA. We saw some great places, did some amazing things and most of all meet/caught up with great friends. Miss you all!!</description>
    <item>
      <title>Iconic Hawaii</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Americas_06/Blog/Entries/2006/9/25_Iconic_Hawaii.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b91dede4-84b7-4e97-a137-c8051e34d50c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2006 18:53:52 +1000</pubDate>
      <description>When you think of Hawaii you think of four things. &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pina_colada"&gt;Pina Colada&#x2019;s&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hawaii_Five-O"&gt;&#x201C;Book&#x2019;em Danno&#x201D;&lt;/a&gt;, Japanese Tourists and last but not least surfing! Today we travelled to Surfing Mecca - North Shore Oahu. Here we took in three of the most infamous beaches on the island - &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sunset_Beach_%28Oahu%29"&gt;Sunset&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Waimea_Bay"&gt;Waimea Bay&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Banzai_Pipeline"&gt;Pipeline&lt;/a&gt;. Although the surf was pretty quiet neither of us wanted to take our chances in the water. I doubt our travel insurance would cover any North Shore surfing injuries!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our other highlight of the day is that at our lunch spot we spotted the actor that plays &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fernando_Sucre"&gt;Fernando Sucre&lt;/a&gt; from the TV series &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prison_Break"&gt;Prison Break&lt;/a&gt;. Felicity and I were both to gutless to ask for his autograph but we got to sit at the table that they dined at!</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object015.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Americas_06/Blog/Entries/2006/9/25_Iconic_Hawaii.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Nemo</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Americas_06/Blog/Entries/2006/9/23_Finding_Nemo.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">11c1524a-df42-4ced-96b5-ef1b4ea60ac5</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2006 13:52:02 +1000</pubDate>
      <description>During our snorkel trip to &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Molokini"&gt;Molokini&lt;/a&gt; today we finally found a famous Hollywood actor. Low and behold it was Gill star fish in the &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Finding_Nemo"&gt;Finding Nemo&lt;/a&gt; movie! We were so stoked! No point obtaining his autograph (the poor guy couldn&#x2019;t hold a pen in his fin) so we just threw him on the grill. Didn&#x2019;t know &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Moorish_Idol"&gt;Moorish Idol&lt;/a&gt; made such good eating!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Enough jokes aside Molokini was an absolute blast. Visibility was amazing - you could see for metres and metres!! The fish were super friendly and were pretty happy to get up close and personal with you. Other snorkelers saw a &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Manta_Ray"&gt;Manta Ray&lt;/a&gt; and a &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Whitetip_reef_shark"&gt;Whitetip Reef Shark&lt;/a&gt;. Glad we didn&#x2019;t come across either of these puppies - sharks scare the bejesus out of me and we all know that Manta Rays and Australian&#x2019;s don&#x2019;t mix!</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object018.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Americas_06/Blog/Entries/2006/9/23_Finding_Nemo.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heeeeeere Fishy Fishy Fishy&#13;</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Americas_06/Blog/Entries/2006/9/21_Heeeeeere_Fishy_Fishy_Fishy.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">68a09780-610d-4523-849e-7166f17312a0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2006 05:19:44 +1000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bert_and_ernie"&gt;Bert and Ernie&lt;/a&gt; would be mighty jealous of the amount of sea-life we&#x2019;ve seen so far in Maui. There was most certainly no need to use their &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pFTjeaDlxDI"&gt;infamous fish calling technique&lt;/a&gt;. We&#x2019;ve been blessed with a whole array of fish and yesterday we even snorkeled with a Sea Turtle. All this is just off the beach in front of the apartment! Pretty crazy stuff!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We&#x2019;ve been really lucky with the weather ever since our arrival on Sunday. We met up with Mum and Dad who&#x2019;ve been on holiday on the islands since the previous Thursday. They&#x2019;ve got a great head start on their tan but Felicity has given them a good run for their money in the last couple of days! It&#x2019;s going to be a tight competition but I&#x2019;m sure she&#x2019;ll come through with the goods. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We&#x2019;ve been staying in the new apartment that mum and dad purchased last year and it&#x2019;s amazing! We&#x2019;ve even giving the kiddy water slide a bit of a workout (Dad included).&lt;br/&gt;&#x2028;The plan for the rest of the week is more tanning, snorkeling and sipping Pina Colada&#x2019;s by the pool. We&#x2019;ll post more photo&#x2019;s of these strenuous activities once we get a chance!</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object002.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Americas_06/Blog/Entries/2006/9/21_Heeeeeere_Fishy_Fishy_Fishy.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleepless in Seattle</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Americas_06/Blog/Entries/2006/9/17_Sleepless_in_Seattle.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2ef1fe57-6b9a-409c-98cd-b1ef15ab2818</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2006 09:37:57 +1000</pubDate>
      <description>There is so much free Internet in Seattle it&#x2019;s no wonder Tom and Meg suffered insomnia - good news that we could finally post our blog!! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Although our stay here in Seattle is short its still been a lot of fun. Friday we headed over to Redmond where Felicity shopped and I had the enjoyment of having lunch on Bill Gates. No doubt he didn&#x2019;t miss that $9.95! &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Today&#x2019;s excitement revolved around flying to the top of the &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Space_Needle"&gt;Space Needle&lt;/a&gt;. Although it&#x2019;s nowhere near a tall as the &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cn_tower"&gt;CN Tower&lt;/a&gt; (1815 feet vs 605) it&#x2019;s still provides just as impressive views of the city skyline. The weather provided a perfect day to take it all in as well! I&#x2019;m just glad that it doesn&#x2019;t have a glass floor as I left my brown undies back in Toronto!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;During our quick Seattle stop over we also got to visit the first ever &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Starbucks_Coffee"&gt;Starbucks&lt;/a&gt; store and we also caught a glimpse of the famous Seattle fish throwers at &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pike_Place_Market"&gt;Pike Place Market&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object017.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Americas_06/Blog/Entries/2006/9/17_Sleepless_in_Seattle.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fond Farewell</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Americas_06/Blog/Entries/2006/9/14_Fond_Farewell.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">239800d4-b7ec-46d5-b850-00d10d8f19c7</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2006 08:19:24 +1000</pubDate>
      <description>Our wonderful Canadian adventures have drawn to a close. Today marked our last full day trekking through the Rockies, as tomorrow we start our journey back to the west coast of the United States!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On our last day here we headed to Maligne Lake and Maligne Canyon. The lake and canyon are the largest of their type in the Rockies. I was a probably a little keen donning shorts this morning as it has started to get a bit chilly. Didn&#x2019;t stop us from having an energetic day trekking around the tranquil lake and fighting off annoying tourists at the canyon.  Snow is forecast for overnight - who knows what sights we&#x2019;ll wake up to!</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object016.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Americas_06/Blog/Entries/2006/9/14_Fond_Farewell.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>EEEE, d MMMM y</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Americas_06/Blog</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>5</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
