<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>The Blog</title>
    <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog</link>
    <description>22 days driving around the sunny state of California in a gas guzzling American car. Drop by the blog and enjoy the carbon footprint increasing ride!</description>
    <item>
      <title>M.I.C.K.E.Y M.O.U.S.E - Mickey Mouse!</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/31_M.I.C.K.E.Y_M.O.U.S.E_-_Mickey_Mouse%21.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">4892ae3f-ac1f-4fbf-9dd6-c333aeaae333</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2009 19:24:01 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>Our last few days take us south to a place called San Clemente where the beach is people free and the water is perfectly blue. Body boarding and sun-baking was going well until someone got crabs! (to be more precise - bitten by one) &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Of course we can&#x2019;t spend all our last days lazing around the water so we ventured to Disneyland. It was a fun experience but frustrating standing in queues all day. We went on a range of rides from the very sedate &#x201C;Winnie the Pooh&#x201D; to the raging waters of &#x201C;Splash Mountain&#x201D;. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On the opposite end of the temperature scale we ventured to the Honda Centre for an ice-hockey match - Anaheim Ducks Vs Vancouver Canucks. It was a fierce match with the home team winning by 5 goals.</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object006.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/31_M.I.C.K.E.Y_M.O.U.S.E_-_Mickey_Mouse%21.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An insider&#x2019;s take</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/31_An_insiders_take.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">a86a600c-1b8f-4a83-bf04-92af386b6caa</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2009 19:23:56 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>Given that this was our second trip to San Francisco, we managed to skip all the touristy sites. Given we were blessed with our own local tour guide we got a great insight into what makes this city tick. Thanks to Rachel for making this leg of the trip wickedly awesome!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We enjoyed visiting the pumpkin patches of Half Moon Bay, the boutique shops of Union Street in Cow Hollow, the restaurants in the Mission and Filmore street as well as the diversity of Cole Valley and the Haight. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It wasn&#x2019;t all about eating and shopping - we marvelled at some great views of the Golden Gate Bridge from Lands End and spent a fantastic day experiencing the newly renovated &lt;a href="http://www.calacademy.org/"&gt;California Academy of Sciences&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object014.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/31_An_insiders_take.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Up, up and away!</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/25_Up,_up_and_away%21.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">42c72e84-528c-482b-98e5-7fa742916c6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2009 14:56:57 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>What better way to enjoy the Californian wine country than via the tranquillity of a hot air balloon? Pity that now neither of us have any eyebrows - I think our face cream contains alcohol!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;All good things seem to require an early rise and hot air ballooning is no different. After a 5:30am start we were briskly on our way to our launch site and before we knew it up in the air enjoying the sights of the Napa Valley. Such an amazing experience - don&#x2019;t forget to check &lt;a href="../The_Pics/Pages/Napa.html"&gt;photos&lt;/a&gt; in our gallery.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The afternoon was even more stressful taking in great wineries such as Silverado, Opus One, O&#x2019;Briens and Taittinger. Following some advice from locals we stopped off at an amazing lunch spot called &lt;a href="http://www.bouchonbakery.com/"&gt;Bouchon Bakery&lt;/a&gt;. We can understand why the Naparians love it as it gave some of the French patisseries we visited last year a run for their money. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Time to head to bed and dream of chocolate macaroons!&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object013.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/25_Up,_up_and_away%21.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Room with a view</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/23_Room_with_a_view.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71bb585c-5ab1-46b0-bd7e-de6fa8990fc7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2009 03:07:59 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>As we woke up to a slightly over cast morning the day seemed to present only one option - time to shop online for prospective engagement rings!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thankfully, for the sake of a certain person&#x2019;s bank account, the cloud burnt off and the weather became perfect. We revised our plans and booked a boat cruise across Lake Tahoe taking in the major sight of yesterday - Emerald Bay. In conjunction with the bay we took a sneak peek at some of the multi million dollar mansions scattered across the shore - certainly impressive and great to get a few ideas should we ever win the lottery. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The cruise presented some breathtaking views and a chance to be out on the water and enjoy this great location from another perspective!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Check out a few more additional photo&#x2019;s in the Lake Tahoe picture album &lt;a href="../The_Pics/Pages/Lake_Tahoe.html"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;!</description>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/23_Room_with_a_view.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To the extreme!</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/21_To_the_extreme%21.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">06e2f7b4-1c0a-4314-be17-43dde22f6ef2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 15:40:10 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>Who would have thought on the drive here amidst the snow and fog that we would wake up the next day to perfect blue sky and sunshine?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The 6 hour drive to Lake Tahoe was jam packed with some wild weather - wind, torrential rain and capped off with a snow storm at 7000 feet! Great fun driving without chains or snow tires - thank god we are in a rental!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Lake Tahoe is an amazing place. The western half resides in the state of California and the eastern half in Nevada. This juxtaposes Californian environmental friendliness with Nevada gambling, casinos and drive through weddings! Tomorrow we&#x2019;ll be tying the knot at a biodegradable chapel!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;More good weather is in store so stay tuned for some great scenic vistas. In the meantime checkout out our latest &lt;a href="../The_Pics/Pages/Lake_Tahoe.html"&gt;photo gallery here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object012.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/21_To_the_extreme%21.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Work the buns!</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/18_Work_the_buns%21.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">23f0fdad-3d04-458d-89e3-2b842e7f6078</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2009 17:15:57 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Richard_Simmons"&gt;Richard Simmons&lt;/a&gt; would be proud! If yesterday&#x2019;s walk wasn&#x2019;t challenging enough then we sure were in for a treat today!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our task (and we chose to accept it) was to walk the famous &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mist_Trail"&gt;Mist Trail&lt;/a&gt; alongside Vernal Fall to enjoy a mid morning snack at &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Emerald_Pool"&gt;Emerald Pool&lt;/a&gt; and the Silver Apron. The Mist Trail, as the name implies, is a rather wet walk up the side of the waterfall along 600 granite steps!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The strenuous slippery walk was well worth the effort to see a great view of Vernal falls. The look back down the valley wasn&#x2019;t half bad either.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Following our decent we drove to Glacier point to find a great sunny spot for lunch. This provided a beautiful panorama of the park including &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Half_Dome"&gt;Half Dome&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/North_Dome"&gt;North Dome&lt;/a&gt; and a selection of snow-capped peaks far in the distance. We also managed a bear sighting at the carpark toilets. Obviously he didn&#x2019;t mind the stench from the composting loos which we will both be glad to see the end of!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The day concluded with a flat 4km walk to Taft point - a view of over 7000 feet above sea level testing our fear of heights.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The highlight of the day had to be hitting the hotel spa - our legs and buns never felt so good! </description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object011.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/18_Work_the_buns%21.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh mountain air    </title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/17_Fresh_mountain_air.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8a890301-3b3f-4a31-a332-14db1a7a80c3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2009 15:56:47 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>Following a long drive we joyfully switched a rain soaked LA for a pristine blue sky Yosemite National Park.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Whist the rain put a dampener on time in LA (which really didn&#x2019;t matter given the fun with had with the Canadians) it was a blessing for our time in Yosemite. Usually at this time of the year the park is dry and the waterfalls run like a leaky tap. But thanks to the rain the park was in full glory with &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yosemite_Falls"&gt;Yosemite&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bridalveil_Fall_%28Yosemite%29"&gt;Bridalveil&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vernal_Falls"&gt;Vernal&lt;/a&gt; Falls all cranking and the meadows sparkling a luscious green!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our first day took us up to Columbia Rock which was a tough steep hike (reminiscent of an episode from &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Man_vs._Wild"&gt;Man vs Wild&lt;/a&gt; - I&#x2019;ve always wanted to be called &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bear_Grylls"&gt;Bear&lt;/a&gt;) through countless switchbacks. Luckily we spent up big at North Face during our shopping exhibitions in LA (reminiscent of an episode from &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sex_and_the_City"&gt;Sex in the City&lt;/a&gt;) so our gear held us in good stead. At the end we were presented with some great views! Check the &lt;a href="../The_Pics/Pages/Yosemite.html"&gt;photo&lt;/a&gt; page for more.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The park is absolutely amazing and the pics (while look good) don&#x2019;t do it justice. Looking forward to the next few days and some more great walking!</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object009.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/17_Fresh_mountain_air.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre Halloween</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/16_Pre_Halloween.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">560fd323-87e7-432a-badf-f8e7374a69e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 16:25:50 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>Sadly our time with the Canadians had come to a close (it was evident that the weather was feeling our sadness as it still continues to bucket down constantly).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We all had an awesome time together and are pumped that it will be less than 12 months until we next meet up.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Californians are primed for Halloween with pumpkin and Halloween paraphernalia taking pride of place everywhere! Can&#x2019;t wait to experience the festivities at the end of the trip.&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object010.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/16_Pre_Halloween.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A hit to the Pocket Book</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/16_A_hit_to_the_Pocket_Book.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3a9fb76b-ed54-4c7f-a700-7abfe731d7e9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2009 01:41:02 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>With the weather set in (and a strong Aussie dollar) there really is only one thing to do - shop!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The ladies hit the shops on Rodeo cleaning up at stores such as Dior, Prada and Jimmy Choo! Luckily the credit card was declined at all of them!</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object008.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/16_A_hit_to_the_Pocket_Book.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beach Bum</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/15_Beach_Bum.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">71ad5ace-1335-40d4-aea4-e87170ffd7ba</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2009 16:25:43 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>Blessed by a touch of nice weather the crew decided to take in the sights of the beaches south of LA. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Whilst not quite hot enough for a swim we managed to fit in breakfast in Manhattan Beach, lunch at Hermosa Beach and dinner all the way down south in Newport Beach (not all in the same day mind you).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Our patch of nice weather was short lived unfortunately. We have been told that it hasn&#x2019;t rained in LA during the month of October since 1966. Pity it decided to buck the trend during our trip and drizzled, bucketed and stormed for about 36 hours straight!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The rain pushes the tourists inside and the homeless out into the open giving an entirely new light on Santa Monica that we all agree has to be the homeless capital of the world!</description>
      <iweb:image href="Media/object007.jpg"></iweb:image>
      <iweb:comment enabled="0" count="0" link="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog/Entries/2009/10/15_Beach_Bum.html#comment_layer"></iweb:comment>
    </item>
    <iweb:dateFormat>EEEE, d MMMM y</iweb:dateFormat>
    <iweb:baseURL>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/California_09/The_Blog</iweb:baseURL>
    <iweb:maximumSummaryItems>10</iweb:maximumSummaryItems>
  </channel>
</rss>
