<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>island hopping</title>
    <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/The_Blog.html</link>
    <description>Although during this trip we’re spending our time on two islands geographically, historically and population wise they are one of stark contrast. Fun fact - Manhattan has 71201 people per square mile, Newfoundland has just 3.</description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.4</generator>
    <image>
      <url>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/The_Blog_files/IMG_1545.jpg</url>
      <title>island hopping</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/The_Blog.html</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>The special day</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/10/10_The_special_day.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">134f0b0c-2491-4b41-90df-e2ec083d81e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2010 09:09:58 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/10/10_The_special_day_files/IMG_3613.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Media/object000_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:250px; height:156px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The day had come, the lead up was all behind us and everyone was in attendance - even Hurricane Earl - today was Steph and James’s wedding!&lt;br/&gt;The area of Gros Morne and Rocky Harbour is simply amazing. Pristine coastlines, steep rocky clifts. To top it off wildlife such as Bears, Moose and Whales can be seen with little effort.&lt;br/&gt;It’s hard to go wrong having a wedding in this setting. The ceremony took place in a small chapel in Norris Point set atop a rise above a natural harbour. Both bride and groom looked amazing - it wasn’t long before they were husband and wife!&lt;br/&gt;The afternoon and evening were action packed. Moose burgers before dinner, Hurricane Earl killing the power at the reception, dancing until 2am in the the morning!&lt;br/&gt;Unfortunately all good things come to an end and as the lights went out on the reception so did our time in Newfoundland. Time to start the long trip home! Goodbye Newfoundland - our little slice of Tassie at the other end of the world!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/10/10_The_special_day_files/IMG_3613.jpg" length="135461" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stephenville</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/9/1_Stephenville.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">d7af2ab8-d0ce-4f11-a030-2f03542201ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 1 Sep 2010 23:00:46 +1000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/9/1_Stephenville_files/IMG_3017.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Media/object004_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:250px; height:156px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Apparently taking the ferry across the Atlantic from Nova Scotia to Newfoundland can be quite harrowing. Whales, ice bergs  - you name it, you could see it. Heck we’re not that far from where the Titanic sunk and we’re sailing on the day of the 25th anniversary that the wreckage of the Titanic was found!&lt;br/&gt;Well... that drama aside our ferry crossing was quite uneventful as the weather was perfect and the sea was calm. &lt;br/&gt;We arrived in Newfoundland to a beautiful sunrise and more magical weather. Steph introduced us to her hometown of Stephenville (pronounced Steph - en - ville after Steph herself). It’s a small town blessed with scenic vistas and windy coastal roads. A slice of Tassie at the other side of the world!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/9/1_Stephenville_files/IMG_3017.jpg" length="69507" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>En route to the Rock</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/31_En_route_to_the_Rock.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3c3b6e9b-ea95-4461-be4c-a60c27a8636a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 22:34:46 +1000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/31_En_route_to_the_Rock_files/IMG_2850.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Media/object005_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:250px; height:156px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Not long after we left Andrew and Mariann at the airport in New York we were welcomed by Steph and James at the Halifax airport. It was great to see them again in real life rather than through the computer on Skype!&lt;br/&gt;Canadians have a big thing for beaver. Seeing this we immediately realised there is some distinct cultural differences between our two countries! If an Australian was that open he/she would be sharing a room with Tiger Woods at the sex clinic.&lt;br/&gt;During our stay in Halifax we were privileged to sample the  world’s best ice cream at &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cows_%28ice_cream%29&quot;&gt;Cows&lt;/a&gt;. Being avid Ice Cream connoisseurs we thought such a statement was setting this little ice cream shop up for serious downfall. To our surprise Cows is true to it’s word - we recommend any ice cream lover to make the trip to one of the many locations &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cows.ca/storelocations/&quot;&gt;throughout Canada&lt;/a&gt;!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/31_En_route_to_the_Rock_files/IMG_2850.jpg" length="150602" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The final roast</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_The_final_roast.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">ba209dbf-9fa4-495a-b587-a76b0d741d92</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 21:49:16 +1000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_The_final_roast_files/DSC_1557.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Media/object053.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:250px; height:156px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;As our amazing time in New York comes to a close we’ve collated our notes and are please to reveal our top 5 coffee spots. We’re pretty confident that each of these cafe’s could hold their own in Melbourne!&lt;br/&gt;1st - 9th Street Espresso 2nd - Stumptown 3rd - Blue Bottle 4th - Cafe Grumpy 5th - Abraco&lt;br/&gt;Given we’d all seen the tourists sites on previous trips we throughly enjoyed seeing it from a new light and spending time in Williamsburg. New York is a great city and something that we’ll hopefully all visit again soon. &lt;br/&gt;With the customary teary farewell in tow (saying goodbye to Andrew and Mariann) we ventured north to take our second island destination - Newfoundland!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_The_final_roast_files/DSC_1557.jpg" length="128428" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Central Park</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_Central_Park.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">009303a3-13c8-48d8-9f0e-9fac1b0ed4c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 21:49:08 +1000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_Central_Park_files/IMG_2655.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Media/object054.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:250px; height:156px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;With eyes wide open after our stroll along the High Line (or was that just the double espressos that the Americans love to serve) we craved more from the parks of New York City. With no surprise that led us to Central Park.&lt;br/&gt;We had good intentions of hiring boats or even bikes at the Boathouse to exert some energy and hopefully offset some of the three course dinners that we’d been devouring. Unfortunately the best we could manage was a relax on the grass sharing some  Ice Cream and Champagne whilst watching NYC locals in Central Park’s Sheep Meadow. I guess it is the thought that counts!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_Central_Park_files/IMG_2655.jpg" length="169876" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The high line</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_The_high_line.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b5afef8a-b042-4f00-adf5-ed697e47bae5</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 21:48:56 +1000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_The_high_line_files/IMG_2341.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Media/object055.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:250px; height:156px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;New Yorkers are quite resourceful. One key example is the High Line - an old raised railway line which has been turned into a public park.&lt;br/&gt;Wanting something different the gang decided it was worthwhile exploring a New York destination that didn’t revolve around shopping, eating or drinking - contentious we know!&lt;br/&gt;Wandering through the streets of Chelsea and the Meatpacking District we stumbled upon the High Line. This once abandoned space is now sparse of weeds and rusting steel and is abundant with gardens, benches and interesting viewing points. It’s a work in progress but sometime in the next couple of years it will be close to 20-30 blocks long! &lt;br/&gt;It’s quite an experience walking through gardens above New York City traffic and feels like you’re miles away from the hustle and bustle below!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_The_high_line_files/IMG_2341.jpg" length="228040" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A day of thirties</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_A_day_of_thirties.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">b6ce0d8d-8c85-4c41-9069-6c49ac4c0fde</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 21:48:47 +1000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_A_day_of_thirties_files/IMG_2520.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Media/object056.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:250px; height:156px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Luckily for her, we all got to celebrate Mariann’s 30th birthday in New York City.&lt;br/&gt;Andrew thoughtfully planned out a number of  ‘30 centric’ activities including a trip to the Thirty Thirty hotel, 30 Street Guitars and 30 Rockefeller Centre. At either end of all this touring was obviously food with breakfast at the W Hotel and an amazing lunch at Nougatine in Central Park. &lt;br/&gt;As seems to be the norm, New York put on a great day - perfect for Mariann on her birthday and even better for our pics atop Rockefeller Centre</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_A_day_of_thirties_files/IMG_2520.jpg" length="116695" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A bridge over untroubled waters</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_A_bridge_over_untroubled_waters.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">6d575a30-479d-4859-8292-f361cd6ee4fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 21:48:26 +1000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_A_bridge_over_untroubled_waters_files/DSC_0978.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Media/object003_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:250px; height:156px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Once upon a time the Brooklyn Bridge was the tallest structure in New York city. Those days are well and truly behind us but the allure of the bridge is still evident.&lt;br/&gt;The walk over the Brooklyn Bridge took us from our adopted Brooklyn home to Manhattan. It’s a pretty magical view but made all that more special with a stop at the famous Brooklyn Ice Creamery (which is conveniently situated at the foot of the Brooklyn side of the bridge) to refuel for the not so strenuous walk.&lt;br/&gt;The weather gods blessed us with warm weather and blue sky which provided a perfect formula for photographers delight. Of course, Andrew and Anthony were more than happy to take full advantage of this. To Mariann and Felicity’s delight (or disgust) the 2000 metre walk ended up taking close on 3 hours - but hey...we got some great pics! &lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/30_A_bridge_over_untroubled_waters_files/DSC_0978.jpg" length="146205" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School of hard (pastry) knots</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/23_School_of_hard_%28pastry%29_knots.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">e75de650-347c-4572-950a-71776deae08b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 14:16:50 +1000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/23_School_of_hard_%28pastry%29_knots_files/IMG_2022.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Media/object002_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:250px; height:156px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Just so we could relive the movie Hitch, we decided to go back to school and take a recreational cooking class where we would learn how to make a dinner party for guests at home. Thankfully we had someone to do all the washing up for us!&lt;br/&gt;Our beer-loving instructor managed to talk our ears off whilst providing us with a few useful tips. We split into 3 groups and shared the cooking of the 9 dishes which involved lots of fun, mess making and almost a trip to the emergency ward! Deciding he was a little cold from the AC, Anthony tried to heat up by using the oven door as a leg warmer. (Don’t worry he’s fine!)&lt;br/&gt;Once complete, we all sat down with some wine (beer for the teacher) and enjoyed our hard work. Despite being a size 0, one of the New Yorkers even went back for thirds and took home the leftovers!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/23_School_of_hard_%28pastry%29_knots_files/IMG_2022.jpg" length="158550" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday night lights ... on Saturday</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/23_Friday_night_lights_..._on_Saturday.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">268f56c2-3a86-4901-a726-c40ff7c40442</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 14:16:26 +1000</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/23_Friday_night_lights_..._on_Saturday_files/IMG_1638.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Media/object001_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:250px; height:156px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Meadowlands_Stadium&quot;&gt;New Meadowlands Stadium&lt;/a&gt; is an 85,000 seat US$1.7 billion complex. We were lucky enough to see the second game ever played there (the first was only a week earlier) with the NY Giants taking on the Pittsburg Steelers. Unfortunately the Giants went down 24 to 17.&lt;br/&gt;American Football is an exceptionally interesting game - Four 15 minute quarters take about 3 hours. Obviously to allow you plenty of time to make multiple trips to the frank stand to get yourself an artery hardening ketchup, mustard and relish covered dog!&lt;br/&gt;Seats were amazing though - seven rows from the front - right on 10 yard line. Great work from AJ scoring these!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/NYC_%26_NFL_10/The_Blog/Entries/2010/8/23_Friday_night_lights_..._on_Saturday_files/IMG_1638.jpg" length="186157" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
