<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>OUR TRAVELS</title>
    <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    <description>Aided with a trusty iPhone and the Lonely Planet translation kit the duo of Felicity and Anthony embark on an epic journey (or rude awakening) to discover French culture.</description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.4</generator>
    <image>
      <url>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Blog_files/IMG_1177-filtered.jpg</url>
      <title>OUR TRAVELS</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    </image>
    <item>
      <title>The Home of Chilli Crab</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/11/8_The_Home_of_Chilli_Crab.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">cb56cfbd-dd2d-414a-892c-e129a548c3e7</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 8 Nov 2008 13:34:52 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/11/8_The_Home_of_Chilli_Crab_files/IMG_2556.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Media/object019_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:212px; height:234px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Given the way our flights worked out we were lucky enough to have a couple of days to stop over in Singapore! It has been an enjoyable stay taking advantage of a little rest and relaxation, a tad of shopping and more good food (which has essentially been the theme of the entire trip!).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Singapore has been a great location to break up the long flight home and fingers crossed will help us fight jet lag and enable a semi-productive work day on Monday! Although to be fair even at full capacity no one can really say that we’re that productive!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So after 18,400 kms in a plane, a tad under 1,000 kms via train and 3,500 kms behind the wheel of our trusty Peugeot our trip has concluded. Pity John Candy isn’t still around to hep us make a sequel to the 80s classic &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0093748/&quot;&gt;Planes, Trains &amp;amp; Automobiles&lt;/a&gt; - I know that he’d make a perfect fit for my character although not sure how Steve Martin will play Felicity....&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Anyway that’s all from us - along with the thousands of kilometres travelled we’ve also taken close on 3,000 pictures so let us know if any of you would like us to tee up an enthralling slide night!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/11/8_The_Home_of_Chilli_Crab_files/IMG_2556.jpg" length="147819" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Her Majesty's Secret Service</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/11/5_Her_Majestys_Secret_Service.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">f5ce82b1-be36-47d5-bf8a-44d659fc1d19</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Nov 2008 10:59:24 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/11/5_Her_Majestys_Secret_Service_files/IMG_2454.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Media/object023_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:248px; height:194px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;With the holiday nearing the end it was time to drop by the great mother land to spend some hard earned coin on some top quality English threads! Coupled with this we’ve also managed to take in a few tourist sites, catch up with some great friends and spend an inordinate amount of time on the London underground!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Although not presented with the best weather (what do you really expect for London in November) it has been an enjoyable conclusion to the trip to wander through the shops and catch up with some great friends not seen for a long time!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Now time to cram the purchases into our overflowing bags, catch the tube to Paddington and check out what the new British Airways Terminal 5 has to offer - hopefully more than the expected delays and lost luggage that the papers have us to believe!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;See you all soon!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/11/5_Her_Majestys_Secret_Service_files/IMG_2454.jpg" length="207088" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cheese, Bog and Whale</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/11/2_Cheese,_Bog_and_Whale.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">c503dfd8-68fb-4913-a18b-518e636dab78</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 2 Nov 2008 21:27:31 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/11/2_Cheese,_Bog_and_Whale_files/IMG_0434.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Media/object022_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:152px; height:182px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Extending from the shenanigans collectively had in Paris the awesome foursome ventured to Andrew and Mariann’s homeland of Bergen, Norway to cause more mayhem. As seen above much time was spent in the supermarkets marvelling at the cultural food differences. Apart from frozen whale another interesting item is Bog in a can. If I knew it was such a hot item I would have put mine in a tin a long time ago!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Its been an amazing few days taking in Bergen and living like the locals. We’ve been hiking in the mountains, eating salmon and wearing enough gortex and thermal layers to make the Michelin Man look thin!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Bergen is a great city and with it’s many similarities to Hobart and Canada combined with the Barry’s/Solberg’s being exceptionally generous and welcoming it truly feels like a slice of home sixteen and a half thousand kilometres away!&lt;br/&gt;</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/11/2_Cheese,_Bog_and_Whale_files/IMG_0434.jpg" length="192854" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Centre of the Cultural Universe</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/10/30_The_Centre_of_the_Cultural_Universe.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1e5db30d-3c2b-4e09-a8bb-4f59eac46d7c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 04:51:42 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/10/30_The_Centre_of_the_Cultural_Universe_files/IMG_1915.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Media/object021_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:364px; height:158px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;As you can no doubt tell with the lack of blog activity for the last 6 days we’ve been having a ball in Paris. Our passion to enjoy this amazing city has not been dampened by the chilly weather! In a sense it is preparing us for what we will face in Bergen!!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We haven’t limited ourselves to just Paris. We ventured to the Champagne region for the day and were able to explore the amazing wineries of Mumm and Moet and Chandon obtaining a real understanding as to how the fizzy juice is put together. We were a little disappointed that we some how missed the wine cask part of the tour...&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As you’ll notice in the photo’s our group of 2 has doubled to 4 as Andrew and Mariann have joined us to enjoy this part of France. Collectively we’re now butchering the local language twice as much as before, twice as likely to tread in dog poo and finally Pain au Chocolat is disappearing in this country twice as fast as it did a few days ago.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As our time in Paris draws to a close so does our time in France. It will be sad to say goodbye - but fingers crossed it will be more of a ‘see you soon’ type of farewell.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Next stop on the trip is the Norwegian town of Bergen - renowned for its fjords and exceptionally strong currency against the Aussie dollar ... great!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/10/30_The_Centre_of_the_Cultural_Universe_files/IMG_1915.jpg" length="175759" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Few Goodbyes</title>
      <link>http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/10/30_A_Few_Goodbyes.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5200981e-2f77-4869-92b6-276ff77e4a93</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2008 04:39:17 +1100</pubDate>
      <description>&lt;a href=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/10/30_A_Few_Goodbyes_files/IMG_1491.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Media/object020_1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;float:left; padding-right:10px; padding-bottom:10px; width:364px; height:173px;&quot;/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;After 3511 kilometres, 197 Euro in tolls and close on 500 Euro in petrol later it was time to hand over our trusty little Peugeot. After close on 3 weeks the little silver rocket had become a member of the family - enabling us to see areas of the country not achievable via any other means of transportation. In handing over the car it was also time to say goodbye to the South of France. We had a great week in the area - minus the few days in Marseille - and it was time to head up to Paris.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Showcasing our enjoyment of France’s second largest city we embarked on the best activity someone can do if they happen to find themselves in Marseille .... leave. With that in mind we jumped on the TGV which in turn catapulted us across the 800 odd kilometres to Paris in just on 3 hours.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On arriving in Paris we immediately noticed a considerable temperature drop - goodbye shorts and tee shirts and hello winter woolies!</description>
      <enclosure url="http://archive.anthonyandfelicity.com/Europe_08/Blog/Entries/2008/10/30_A_Few_Goodbyes_files/IMG_1491.jpg" length="163727" type="image/jpeg"/>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
